Manoj Khatri

23 Summer Drive, Scarborough, ON M1K3E3 | (647)-766-9359 | manojkhatri2934@gmail.com

Overview

With strong attention to detail and accuracy, important ability to operate independently, strong and reliable individual with a result- driven approach. Willing to learn any skills that doesn't fall under my experience and work hard to meet the expectations of the company.

Availability:

- Day and night shifts on Saturday and Sunday
- Nights shifts on Wednesday and Friday and day shift on monday

Education:

- HIGH SCHOOL(SCIENCE) | 2020 | HIMALAYAN WHITE HOUSE INT'L S.S
- Currently pursuing diploma in computer programming at Seneca College.

Skills and abilities:

- Able to work independently and as a team, as assigned
- Understanding and communicating oral and written instructions
- Able to maintain a positive, professional and constructive tone with team members and management
- Excellent customer service and communications
- Perform cashier duties

Experience:

VIEWPOINT RESTURANT, LAZIMPAT-30, NEPAL

Role: Kitchen helper (part time) July 2019- Jan 2020

- Serving costumers as per their needs
- Helping in kitchen: cutting vegetables, meat and kitchen management.

KATHMANDU CITY MART, LAZIMPAT-30, NEPAL

Role: Cart attender (full time)

April 2020-January 2021

- Managing various carts and maintain availability of carts.
- Co-ordinating with customers and provide personalize service.
- Co-ordinating with team and ensure appropriate stock of supplies.

Role: Cashier (full time)

Feb 2021- Feb 2022

- Operating cash registers and process payments according to company procedure.
- Providing answers to products related queries and handling complaints.
- Being polite and generous with costumers.